<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sage&#39;s Succurity Blog</title>
    <link>https://succurity.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sage&#39;s Succurity Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 15:36:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://succurity.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DNS Tunneling with Iodine</title>
      <link>https://succurity.com/post/offsec/dns-tunneling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 15:36:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://succurity.com/post/offsec/dns-tunneling/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes during pentest engagements in restricted networks, we might need access to the internet. Internet access could be used to exfil info or retrieve a tool or script. Because of the state of those networks, no data can leave the network boundry. Security is hard and although the internet can be blocked, DNS is sometimes overlooked and DNS queries could still work. This is were we can use DNS Tunneling to circumvent any blocks that have been put in place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pentesting Field Guide</title>
      <link>https://succurity.com/post/offsec/pentesting-field-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:33:58 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://succurity.com/post/offsec/pentesting-field-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As an OSCP student, I frequently searched the web for notes, tips, advice, or anything that would help me learn the necessary skills to pass the exam. This &lt;em&gt;field guide&lt;/em&gt; started off as that, a collection of gathered OSCP notes from around the web, but as I learn more, this post serves as a place to document everything.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox | Mango Writeup</title>
      <link>https://succurity.com/post/write-ups/htb-mango/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 13:11:24 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://succurity.com/post/write-ups/htb-mango/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mango. Oh man. Getting user access on this box was intense. I personally have weak web exploitation skills when it comes to web attacks, so this box did teach me alot. In terms of realism, this box was definitely real-world related and I can apply everything I learned to any future pentests I will do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Buffer Overflows</title>
      <link>https://succurity.com/post/offsec/intro-to-buffer-overflows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 11:46:59 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://succurity.com/post/offsec/intro-to-buffer-overflows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SLMail is an awesome choice of software to easily practice creating and exploiting buffer overflows. If you need to practice Buffer Overflows for your OSCP, then hopefully this tutorial can help you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to RFID Hacking</title>
      <link>https://succurity.com/post/rfid-hacking-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:12:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://succurity.com/post/rfid-hacking-primer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This primer is for those that are interested in RFID pentesting. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start or if you are looking into RFID &amp;ldquo;hacking&amp;rdquo;, I hope you can take something away from all of this. I am in no way an expert and I am still learning as much as I can about this technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C Shells for Routers &amp; Gateways</title>
      <link>https://succurity.com/post/offsec/c-shells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 20:24:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://succurity.com/post/offsec/c-shells/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today at work, we made these two C Shells for embedded devices that run busybox. One is a bind shell and the other is a reverse shell.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://succurity.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 18:33:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://succurity.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Rafael Munoz and I am a lifelong security student. I&amp;rsquo;ve created this blog to help me document all the cool things I learn in security, as well as share a little bit of my life with you.
About This Blog Credit where credit is due so thanks to @kakawait for this beautiful theme you see here. This blog is built using Hugo and is hosted on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>